It was the Ching Dynasty,
清朝咸丰年间
an unhappy scholar of Guang Dong Province,
在广东省宝安县有一个失意的秀才
who couldn't pass the country exam for the 14th time
考了十四次的乡试都没有考中
Even his wife had run away for good
连老婆都跟人走了
He was so sad and depressed,
在悲愤之余，他把心一横
he killed himself in an old temple
干脆到古庙悬梁自杀
But due to an unintended but
但是由于在一次无意之间
pre-arranged co-incident
其实是故意安排的
This ghost
这位心中有冤
who could not yet be reincarnated
而不能够投胎转世的冤鬼
was brought to the city by three girls
给三个女学生带了出市区
So something extraordinary but quite normal
而他们之间发生了一段不寻常
happened between them
但是很正常的关系
From the three girls
朱秀才从三个女学生身上
Chu learn the way of life
体会到做人的可贵
He felt at ease all at once
心理的冤屈当场消失
He had decided to reincarnate & become a new man
于是他决定投胎转世，重新做人
This newly born "Happy ghost"
而投胎之后的开心鬼
For the good deeds he had done,
因为他前世多积阴德
was a man of many gifts
所以得天独厚，天渊之别，与众不同
No milk today!
没有奶奶吃啰！
Satin's baby!
鬼胎！
Is it fun?
怎么样，好不好玩？
He can't catch me
他老是打不到
Teacher!
老师！
You're doomed!
你该死了！
Although Sam Hong, the happy ghost,
虽然开心鬼投胎成康心贵
had supernatural powers
有超自然的能力
He was not a happy man
但是他从来没有开心过
Packing up, Miss?
老师，你的书掉啦！
The early bird gets the worms!
福无双至，祸不单行！
Wait for me, Chairman!
会长…等等我！
Do I look like Akina?
我像不像中森明菜？
You look like Shitkina!
像，像猪母菜，拜拜！
Bitch!
三八！
Wait for me, Chairman!
会长，你慢一点啦！
Chairman!
会长！
Go away...
让开…！
I'll have fish balls!
鱼丸！
Then for just $5, it's cheap!
真便宜，一串才五块！
Uncle Tang is such a nice man!
邓伯，你真是好人！
Uncle doesn't need that much money
阿伯一个人不需要赚很多钱
It's just for you!
给你们赚到了！
Drumstick please!
我要鸡腿！
US$20
二十块！
Thank you!
谢谢！
What a loss of face, Chairman
会长，这次你可糗大了
It's a shame!
真没面子哎！
Are you new here?
你是新来的？
What's your name?
叫什么名字？
My name is Yiu, King Yiu
我姓姚，叫姚姚姚姚琼
What a name? Are you from Taiwan?
怎么你名字有五个字，你是山地人？
Or Red Indian!
一定是印第安人！
I'm from Guang Zhou, the new comer
我是潮州人，是新来的插班生
The new comer!
是新来的？
| love to take care of newcomers
我最喜欢照顾新来的同学了
You're in luck!
你走运啰！
Do you want to join the club?
姚琼女士，想不想入会呀？
I've no religion!
我没有宗教信仰！
No, don't the church!
不是教会呀！
You mean a triad society?
不会是黑社会吧？
No! No! No!
不！ 不！ 不！
It's the Meanies Club!
是卑鄙会！
The Meanies Club?!
卑鄙会？
That's right and I'm the Chairman!
没错，我就是卑鄙会的会长！
The Vice Chairman!
我是副会长！
The Deputy Vice Chairman!
我是副副会长
The goal of the Club is...
我们卑鄙会的宗旨是…
Do only the mean things
不够卑鄙的事不做
The meaner the better
越卑鄙的事情越做
But eating and sleeping are not mean
那么吃饭、睡觉都不算卑鄙
Why do you do it?
你们也在做啊！
Ha!
哈！
Ha! Ha!
哈哈！
Ha! Ha! Ha!
哈哈哈！
Eating in class, sister
小妹妹，上课的时候吃零食
Sleeping in the exam, aren't they mean?
考试的时候打瞌睡，算不算卑鄙呀？
It's awful!
你们简直是过份嘛！
Look, if you refuse to join us,
告诉你，不加入我们卑鄙
you are mean to us
就是对我们卑鄙
When you are mean to us, we will be...
你卑鄙我们，我们卑鄙会就…
mean to you!
卑鄙你！
It's alright!
没事！ 没事！
Dancing!
舞照跳！
Singing!
歌照唱！
Copying in the examination!
考试照样抄抄抄！
Who do you think would dare
你们猜猜看
to take Miss Lim's place
林黛玉被我们气走了以后
After we've driven her away?
是那个够胆来接她的位子啊？
Miss Lam! Miss Shark! Miss Chin and Miss Flatage!
林黛玉！ 大白鲨！ 秦菲菲！ 洗衣板！
Miss Gossip! Miss Ugly! Miss Crocodile!
阿匹婆！ 鳄鱼精！ 老巫婆！
We've driven 7 teachers
我们这个学期
away this year
已经赶走了七个老师了哎！
Form Master, your name is weakness!
班导师，你的名字是弱者！
Bad news, my lord!
会长，大事不好了！
I've just heard the news from the teacher's room
我刚从教务处听到个消息
The new Form Master is coming today
新来的班导师已经到了
It's no big deal!
有什么了不起嘛！
It is! "He is not a woman"
问题是他不是女人
That's right, not a woman
对呀，他不是女人
| know... he must be a man!
我知道了，那他一定是男的啰！
Nuts, of course he is a man!
你真蠢啊，不是女人，当然是男人啦
Beside Arts Subject
听说他除了教我们学科以外
he also teaches PT!
还教我们体育呀！
A man!
男人教体育！
He might take advantage of us!
容易被吃豆腐！
You? Forget it!
吃你豆腐？不嫌腻呀？
Unbelievable!
要死啦！
Help!
救命呀！
Look, we'll kill her this time!
你们看，咬死她啦！
Chairman, please don't be mean to me
会长，我求求你们不要再卑鄙我了
I've decided to join your club
我决定加入你们的卑鄙会
Okay, you have my permission to be mean like us
好了，以后你就是卑鄙会的会员
The target now is to be
现在我们的目标
mean to the new Form Master
是要卑鄙那位新来的老师
What does he look like?
你们猜，新来的老师长什么样子？
What'll a nice teacher be doing in a school like this?
来这儿的还会有什么好东西呀！
| hope he is tougher than Rocky
我希望他俊过谭咏麟
and handsome as Robert Redford
帅过周润发
That would be perfect
那我就心满意足了
For me, he should be slim and tall
我希望他最好是玉树临风，高高瘦瘦
honest with
有内涵，有气质的老实型男人
excellent taste
那就好了呀！
Look!
你们看！
Class, I'm your new Form Master!
各位同学，我是你们新来的班导师
My name is Sam Hong!
我叫康心贵！
This is my first job after College of Education
这也是我师大毕业以后第一份工作
| hope we can get along happily!
希望我们大家能够合作愉快
Hey you, no drinking in class
这位同学，上课的时候不能喝汽水
You can't listen to the radio
也不能听音乐
He's mean to us!
他一来就跟我们作对！
He's a dead duck!
他死定了！
Let me show you some exercises
请大家排好队，跟我做体操
I'll demonstrate and you'll follow
我示范一次，大家跟着我做
Come on! It's old fashion!
老师，你土不土呀？
We're not kindergarten!
你以为你教幼儿园哪！
These are the basic warm-up only
这是最基本的热身运动
Can you show us something more difficult?
做个难点的动作给我们看看
I'm afraid it's too difficult for you
我怕动作太难了，你们会做不到的
You're not scared, are you?
怕你做不到哦！
Okay, watch!
好，看着！
Lets do it!
跟着做呀！
Okay!
做！
Today I'll show you how to play basketball
接着我教大家打篮球
This is a basketball
这个就是篮球
Bull shit!
废话！
It's called a basketball
篮球之所以叫做篮球
because there is a basket and a ball
就是因为它有篮，又有球
Would you please tell me
这位同学，你可不可以告诉我
What is a basketball?
篮球是什么？
It's round and it bounces!
是圆的，会弹的！
He's insulting your IQ, Chairman!
会长，他简直是侮辱你的IQ嘛！
That's right, your IQ is just that much
不错，以你的IQ就知道这么多
A international Standard Basketball
国际标准的篮球
it's diameter is 28 cm and weigh 0.5 kg
直径有2.8公分，重量是0.5公斤
As for bounce...
弹力嘛…
It's no use talking, sir
老师，打球用讲的没用
You've got to shoot through the basket!
要射得准才有用啊！
Good...!
好啊…！
Not bad, considering your age
好…看不出你小小年纪，功夫这么好
Quit the sweet-talk!
老师，你别狗眼看人低！
Sweet-talk?
什么？
Can you show us
老师，有两下子就射两球
a couple of shots, sir!
让我们开眼界！
Tell you
可声明在先
But save your applause of I miss!
老师射不进去，你们不可以笑呀！
That's a shot you should learn!
这一球你要好好学哦！
Hurray for the master!
好啊…老师好棒，好棒啊！
I've fallen back for lack of practice
好久没练球，技术退步很多
Hurray for the master, encore...!
老师好棒啊，安哥…！
Teacher is this!
老师是乌龟！
Hey! I'll beat you, bitch
喂！ 三八，信不信我打你
I'm beautiful...
扮靓，好靓…
Here comes the teacher...!
老师来了，快点坐好…！
Good morning, class!
各位同学，大家好！
Good morning, sir!
老师好！
Keep quiet, everybody!
安静一点，请大家安静点儿！
Quiet!
安静！
Come on... make some noises!
吵啊，大家吵啊！
Roll Call!
现在开始点名！
Pretty Wong!
黄带金！
Two Prettys in the class?
怎么班上有两个黄带金呀？
No, I want to go to the toilet!
不是啦，老师，我想去尿尿！
Me too!
我也是啊！
Okay and hurry back!
好…快去快回！
Yan Tao May!
简静美！
Stop playing games, will you?
你们不要耍我好不好？
| just want to tell you
我们是想告诉你
May Yan has just walked out!
刚刚出去尿尿那个是简静美呀！
Yeah!
是呀！
Alright, don't raise your hand
好，以后没叫你的名字
unless you're called!
你不要举手啊！
Thatcher!
戴卓怡！
King Yiu!
姚琼！
Okay, let's try the new way
好，换另外一个方式点名
Absentees please raise their hands!
没来的同学请举手！
So everyone is present!
好，那就表示没有人缺席
Then let's start the lecture
现在开始上课
Is this the welcome present for your new teacher?
难道这就是你们欢迎新老师的礼物？
No wonder you've driven 7 teachers away already?
怪不得半个学期气了七位老师
We didn't drive them away
不是给我们气走的
They're weak
是她们意志薄弱
They can't stand the new generation
受不了潮流的冲激
nor the pressure of modern society
挡不住时代的压力
Why do you enjoy tricking people?
你们怎么这样喜欢整人呢？
Why don't you study while you can?
有这样好好的环境，却不好好的读书
The poor in the ancient time
古时候的人没钱读书
Ancient people break a wall for light to study
甚至凿壁偷光都是为了读书
Break what wall?
凿壁偷光？
To expose what the neighbours are doing?
那隔壁房子不就透光了吗？
It must be exotic
那种光应该叫做春光
"Blowup"!
“春光外泄”！
You have a dirty mind, sir!
老师，你好色啊！
Dirty mind? Who?
色？谁很色啊？
The master!
老师好色！
Dirty stories in class
老师上课谈色情
I'll report you to the Head Mistress!
我去告诉校长，你惨啦！
Go back to your seat!
回位子去！
Go back!
回去就回去！
You don't have to yell!
这么凶！
Who're you trying to scare?
打烂桌子吓学生！
Silly nonsense!
混账！
Sam, get hold of yourself
心贵，你要控制你自己
Teaching is not done with violence
教书不是靠打的
| didn't hit them
我没有打她们
| just hit the table!
我只是打桌子嘛！
I'd rather you hit them
我宁愿你打学生
They would be cured
打伤学生医得好
A broken table can't be repaired!
你打坏桌子修都修不好啦！
They may be naughty!
就算顽皮吧！
But you shouldn't use violence!
你也不能使用暴力，太冲动了！
Students coming to school
学生到我们学校来读书
are our customers
也就是我们的顾客
You're the salesman!
你是售“课”员哪！
You can't treat customers like this!
没有理由对我们的顾客动粗！
He takes the school for a department store
副校长把我们学校比喻为百货公司
| disagree!
我不同意！
But I think it's more like a hospital
我觉得学校就好像一间医院
Some come in and some go out
每年有人出，有人进
Some alive, some died!
有人生，有人死！
| wish to have peace
我总希望这间医院平平静静
and quiet in the hospital
安安宁宁
I'm Sorry!
对不起！
Try to love your patients
要用爱心照顾这些病人
Yes!
是
I'm many years your senior
虽然我比你高几届
But we are from the same college
但我们同时在师大毕业的
Please don't fail me!
我不希望你出漏子
Yes!
是！
That's all!
没事了，出去吧！
Cost of repair will be deducted from your salary
那张桌子的钱会从你薪水里面扣的
What happen?
老师，怎么啦？
So you've lost your appetite?
那班猴婴仔弄得你没胃口了？
No!
不是！
Let's face it
你也不要不承认了
You're not the first one
其实你也不是第一个
They're still kids
她们几个没有什么啦！
They are lovely!
其实她们活泼、可爱，好玩哪！
They like to play games and have fun!
爱作弄老师，开开玩笑啦！
| can't stand it anymore!
我看我也做不久了！
But that will lead you nowhere!
老师，你“既来之，则安之”吧！
Actually, their tricks are really simple
其实她们的把戏我最清楚
The same old things
她们整人的绝招就是那几样
Chalk, duster, glue and needles...
粉笔、粉刷、图钉、胶水，就是这样
Would you please give me some advice
阿伯，你可不可以告诉我一个绝活
so that I'll be well-prepared for them
不要让她们把我当小狗一样的耍
Sit down
你放心吃饭吧
and let me tell you
我会慢慢的告诉你方法
"I'll be with you all night"
（要对足一千个晚上）
Disgusting!
讨厌！
Who looks nice?
那个正点呀？
None!
没有正点的！
The girls from St Holy are famous for their quality!
将就点吧，如果说气质嘛！
They are the best
这桌子的码子起码比隔壁那群
in the neighbourhood!
山东大妞好太多啰！
Oh my God!
哎唷我的妈呀！
What about the one in white
其实那个穿白裙子的蛮正点的
They're all in white nuts!
对面四个都穿白裙子的，傻瓜！
| am talking about...
我是说…
The one on the left hand side
最左边的那个
She has such a good appetite
那么会吃，迟早会被吃垮的
| like the one next to her
我就喜欢她隔壁那一个
She's the chairman of their Meanies Club!
那个是她们卑鄙会会长，戴卓怡！
She's tough!
好凶悍哪！
But it's exciting too!
凶悍才够刺激！
| like the one with the mirror
照我看，那个照镜子的才是最好的
Chairman!
会长
The three stooges
那边有三只菜鸟
are staring at us!
两眼一直盯着我们不放
The monks from the Boy's school
是对面和尚学校的小子
Operation Mean, Chairman!
会长，我们采取卑鄙行动
It's too late, they've made their move!
太迟了，他们已经行动了！
Go!
走啊！
...No...
我…不…！
They...
他们…约你们…
Calm down, kid!
“弟弟”镇定点！
Sit down!
不要怕嘛，坐下！
Don't let your nerve ruin your image, boy!
越发抖就越破坏形象，那可就糗大啰
Is it your
看你那么羞答答的
first time?
是不是情窦初开呀？
Yes... No...
是我…不…！
They want to date you...
是他们想约你…
Me?
我？
No, all of you!
不，想约你们去拍拖！
To have a date?
拍拖？
To go for a walk!
不…是逛街…！
To go for a walk, like holding hands?
逛街，拍拖，手牵手啊？
No problem
没问题！
People say once you get acquainted
俗话说，一回生，两回熟
You can be good friends!
三回可上床！
But we want to go in a car
不过我们要有汽车接送才行
Do you have one, boy?
你有没有啊，小子？
Of course we have one!
有，我们高大少有车！
It's my father's car...
其实那部车是我老爸的…
He bought it for you!
你老爸买给你的嘛！
When will you be free?
小妞，几时有空呀？
Tonight!
今晚啊！
No, it's Grandma's Birthday!
不可以呀，今晚我婆婆过生日
My mother says...
我妈妈说…
Quit the bullshit!
不要婆婆妈妈的啦，就这么说定了
Let's make it tonight after school or never
今晚学校门口见，不见不散哦！
Let's go!
走吧！
Bye!
再见！
Do they mean it?
他们来真的哎！
What next, Chairman?
会长，咱们怎么做？
We'll teach them a lesson tonight
今晚实行MOVE THEM！
I mean a lesson!
整垮他们！
They should have it!
就是宰了他们！
My father needs the car
我老爸说今晚八点前
before eight tonight
一定把车交回给他送面包
or he'll kill me!
要不他会宰了我哎！
Shut up! They're coming!
不要吵啦，她们来了！
They're coming!
他们还是真的来了哎！
This is it!
这是我面包王子的坐车
A 7-seater, Rolls Royce, spacious!
七人座，够宽敞！
In please!
请上车！
You've done it this time!
这次你有面子！
It's exciting to sit at the front
你们两位坐前面，前面够刺激
But it's safer to sit at the back
你们两位坐后面，后面够安全
For you
送给你的
Where is my flower?
我的花在那里？
Have a drink!
喝汽水啦！
It's my father's...
那是我老爸的…
His father reserves for his guests
是他老爸特地买来请你们喝的
Help yourself with the bread!
后面有面包，随便用！
My father...
那也是我老爸…
Your father told you to drive carefully!
你老爸叫你专心开车！
Let me introduce ourselves
我们还没有自我介绍
My name is Poon On
我叫潘再安
Everybody calls me Don Juan
人人都叫我再世潘安
He is Daisy Ko!
他呐他叫高大绥
What? Dizzy Ko?
高大衰？
My Chinese name is terrible!
别讲中文名那么老土啦！
My English name really suits me
我的英文名字却很威风
It's Michael Jackson
我叫迈可杰克逊
Ko!
高！
What's yours?
小妞，你呢？
I'm Akina!
我最近改了个名字叫明菜
Akina?
明菜呀？
I used to be Aisy!
别名叫宝珍！
Switch places with me!
泡疹啊？我跟你换位子！
Anything to do with AIDS?
你别搞了，叫宝珍就是有泡疹
My name is Herby
我叫林炳，难道就是有淋病呀！
Where're you taking us, handsome?
你到底带我们去哪里玩哪？
To Paidu!
去新北投呀！
We'll go swinging at the park!
去新北投温泉公园荡秋千呀！
You go yourself!
叫你妈带你去玩好了
You boys are not being romantic!
没想到你们这么不浪漫哪！
Romantic?
浪漫？
Romance is a summer day's sunset
浪漫就是在一个金黄色的夏日黄昏
Going to the beach
开着车去海边
listening to the waves
听听海浪的声音
Watching the sea
看看浪花的美姿
Leaving your footprint in the sand
在沙滩上留下一行行的脚印
Daisy, go for the romantic ride!
大绥，那我们赶快开车去浪漫吧！
I'm scared
吓死我了
It's lovely!
好漂亮！
Do you know what romance is now?
什么叫浪漫？
Of course, I always knew!
懂啊！ 就是浪来得好慢，叫做浪漫哪
Yeah, that's really romantic!
这个才是真正的浪漫！
Not yet, it's even morn if we go swimming!
还不是哪，跳下去游泳才真是浪漫！
Count me in!
好啊！ 我想游哎！
Me too!
我也想呀！
Hey, how about it?
怎么样？你们游不游啊？
We don't have our swimsuit!
不可以呀，我们没有带游泳裤！
Either do we!
我们也没有带游泳衣呀！
But the coast is clear!
怕什么！ 这边又没人！
Let's strip!
快，还不脱衣服？
Aren't you coming?
小珍，来游啊！
No, it's too cold!
不要，这水好冷啊！
No, it's not cold!
不冷，这水不冷！
Let me show you!
我试给你看！
The water is nice!
这水好暖呀！
It's like a spring!
简直就是温泉呐，温泉呐！
Come on down!
你们也下来浪漫呀！
Grab the clothes!
拿走衣服上车
What're you doing?
你们干什么？
Come on!
快，快呀
Oh! Don't take our clothes!
喂！ 衣服还给我们啊！
Let's go, Chairman!
快点，快点开车嘛，快点
Don't go!
不要走
Bye!
再见！
Oh no, my father's car!
我老爸的车！
You see!
你睇！
So many tickets?
这么多罚单哪？
Oh no...
完了…！
Look!
你看！
That's the end of me
这下子可真玩完了
I'm sorry, father!
惨了，老爸！ 我对不起你！
We have fixed those monks
我们这样子整那三个和尚
real good this time!
真是够卑鄙的了！
Shut up and give me a hand!
好了…废话少说，过来帮忙！
What are you doing?
会长，这做什么？
This is the latest BB Glue
最新的瞬间黏着剂
It will tear his pants off!
老师坐下去，连内裤都会扯破
Aren't we going too far?
好像太过份了嘛！
Too far?
过份？
You haven't been too cooperative lately!
我看你最不上道是真的！
Aren't you?
是不是你不上道？
No!
没有呀！
In order to show your loyalty to the club
为了表示你对卑鄙会的忠心了嘛
You are to put this "Thing" in his drawer
这一只就由你放在老师的抽屉里了
Don't panic, it's the latest Japanese Product
不用怕，这只是日本最新产品
Soft plastic toy mouse
超薄塑料假老鼠
Looks real!
很逼真的！
It looks real!
好像真的哎！
It's ugly!
恶心死啦！
Hurry and put it in his drawer
放进老师抽屉里
and scare the hell out of him
保证把他吓得半死
Hurry up!
快走呀，快去放嘛
Keep on, Keep on!
继续油油满它
Here come the teacher!
老师来了哎！
Damn!
失败！
Good morning, class!
各位同学早！
Thank you very much for your welcoming applause!
谢谢你们用二十一响礼炮来欢迎我！
Here are your homework book
这里是你们的功课簿
Give them the homework
班长，请你发给她们
Stand still!
站住！
Are you on roller skate?
你为什么穿溜冰鞋？
We're living in
老师，现代是工业社会
a fast commercial world
讲求效率、速度
What's wrong with efficiency?
我发簿子的方法不对吗？
Nothing, go on!
没有不对，继续发！
Sir, I...
老师呀，我想…
Raise your hand before you talk
班上规矩，发言之前请举手
Only suspects raise their hands
只有小太妹被警察搜身的时候
for the police!
才高举双手！
Can we turn on the fan?
好热哦，可不可以开电风扇？
Yes!
可以！
We lost again!
又失败了！
It's Art today
这堂是美术课
You will sketch a person
我希望大家画一张人像素描
Entitled "The one you love"
题目是“一个我最喜爱的人”
So sketch you loved ones
希望把你们最喜欢的人画出来
It can be your father, mother
可以画你爸爸、妈妈
or teacher
老师…
Oh no, not the teacher
不要画老师，千万不要画老师
Shit, he put on two pairs of pants!
下流，穿两条裤子！
Damn, damn, damn!
失败加失败！
That's the end of that!
好，到此为止了！
| hope this kind of trick
我希望整人的游戏
will not happen in this classroom again
从此不要在班上出现
We don't know sketching, Sir!
老师，我们不会画人像哎！
Would you care to show us?
你可不可以示范一下
Yeah, demonstrate!
是啊，老师，是不是可以示范一下？
Alright...!
好…！
The duster is in the drawer
老师，粉刷在抽屉里面
Yeah, the drawer!
对呀，就在抽屉里面
OK...
好…！
Oh my god, it's a mouse!
老鼠，好大的老鼠！
A real mouse
这真是老鼠，我最怕老鼠了
I'm so scared!
怕怕，小生怕怕！
It's a fake, dummy!
假老鼠，傻瓜！
This one is real
你那只是真的
The fake is over here
假的在这里
Help...!
救命呀…！
What's happening?
发生什么事啦？
Nothing!
没事没事，校长，没什么事！
There's a mouse in the class!
只不过班上来只老鼠！
Mouse?
老鼠？
Help...!
救命呀…！
I'm so scared!
我最怕老鼠了
Mr Hong told us to join the Aquatic Meet
康老师真土，要我们参加什么水运会
He said he'll teach us to swim
还教我们游泳
We haven't been too good to him!
我觉得你们对他太坏了啦！
Which said are you on?
我觉得你整天护着他
You're not having a crush on him, are you?
真是情窦初开，老师都爱
Of course not!
你别胡说了！
We're no good at swimming
游泳输她们
We play volleyball better
排球那是我们的天下
At the inter-school competition
暑假前的校际排球赛
We'll be the champion!
一定要拿冠军！
Don't you recognise us?
还记不记得我们？
Not with your clothes on!
穿上衣服不认识啰！
You got him into real bad trouble!
你们把他害得好惨哪！
My father beat me up for it
惨点被我老头打成脑震荡
What do you want?
你们想怎么样？
Want?
怎么样？
To get even!
想报仇！
You better apologise
想没事，就跪在这儿瞌头认错
Apologise? Ha!
认错？哈！
Ha! Ha!
哈！ 哈！
Ha! Ha! Ha!
哈！ 哈！ 哈！
Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha!
哈！ 哈！ 哈！ 哈！
They're laughing at us
还敢笑我们，教训她，上！
Where're you people from?
站住，你们是哪间学校的？
Can't you see their school ties, Sir
老师，看他的领带，上面有绣学校名
So you're from the neighbourhood
原来你们是隔壁男校的
You three mad dogs
你们三只疯狗
What do you want from our girls?
进来想非礼我的学生呀？
So you're their teacher?
你是老师呀？
Did you teach them?
你怎么教你学生的？
To be a thief?
教她们做贼呀？
Can you prove it?
你有什么证据呀？
They're the witnesses! This is your proof
他们两个是证人，这是物证
| don't care what's wrong?
我不管谁对谁错
But I'll give you one minute to disappear
限你们一分钟之内，消失！
What if we don't?
不走又怎么样？
You won't?
你不走？
That's right!
就不走！
If you don't leave, we will!
你们不走，我们走！
Running away!
想跷头啊！
We'll beat him, we outnumber him 3 to 1
不要怕，我们三个打他一个，稳赢的
Who threw the ball at me?
你们哪个用球打我的？
Who do you think you are?
你是老师就嚣张呀！
You're only a teacher!
当老师很吊呀！
What I really hate is a teacher
我从小被老师吓唬大的
Because...!
我最讨厌老师了！
Running away!
跷头！
Let's go...!
走…！
None of my business!
不关我的事！
Go to hell!
你去死吧你！
You were wrong to break the table
上次你打烂桌子已经就不对了
You even beat up our neighbour's students,
这回你还打伤隔壁的学生
what's up?
你怎么解释？
| didn't mean it
我不是故意的
It's embarrassing
我很难做人
We've such a good relationship with their school
两间学校的关系一向都很好
and now their Form Mistress calls to complain
而且人家导师老老师打电话来告状
And request compensation!
要你赔医药费，气死我了！
| know, I'll apologise to her in person
我知道，我会亲自去道歉的
Are you Miss Lo?
请问那位是老老师呀？
Yes, I am!
我就是呀！
Who are you, mister?
请问你是哪一位呀？
My name is Hong
小生姓康
I'm their class mister...
不是小生，是先生…
I'm their teacher!
就是老师啦！
The school next door
我是隔…隔壁学校…
So you're the one who hurt my boys
原来你就是打伤我班上学生的人哪？
What're you doing here?
你到这儿来做什么？
Nothing... I just came here to...
没事没事，我只是想…
What?
你想干什么嘛你？
Nothing... let me help you!
没事没事，我扶你起来，我扶你！
You've lost your sleeve
没事没事，只是只袖子
Let me help you put it back on
来…我帮你穿好！
Don't come any closer!
你不要过来，不要过来！
| just want to help you It's alright!
没事没事，我帮你穿好！
Help you...
来，穿好…！
No!
不必了！
You are so annoying, go away!
你真烦了，走开！
Let me fix it!
没事没事，我把它挂好
Did Miss Lo make a complaint to their school?
不晓得老老师有没有去抗议呀？
He tried to kill the witness!
你想杀人灭口呀！
It's alright It's a misunderstanding!
没事没事，是误会呀！
Don't go away!
你们不要走啊！
I'll help clean it up!
没事没事，我帮你擦干
| clean it up for you!
我帮你擦，擦…！
No one will notice it,
没事没事，只有我一个人看见
| didn't mean it
我不是故意的
Can't you do anything right?
你不是故意的就弄成这个样子
Alright, it's not alright
没事没事，拆了别人教员休息室
to smash their restroom
你还说没事
They complain that you're a sex-maniac
别人要告你，说你是色情狂
You tried to rape and smash their room
强奸未遂，捣毁教室
| think we can not tolerate a person
校长，我们绝对不允许
who has ruined the reputation of our school
有人破坏我们学校的名誉
| really think...
我认为呐，应该…
Let me handle it
朱老师，这件事我来处理
You're in luck!
心贵，你命好
Miss Lo will not pursue the result of this case
幸亏老老师心好，不再追究这件事
But you'll pay the indemnities
但是打烂的东西要照赔
But please remember, don't do it again
希望这次是最后一次
or I'll not be able to help you
再有下次，我也没办法再帮你了
Thank you, Madam!
谢谢学姐！
About your salary of this month
这个月的薪水
$2 left after deduction?
就剩这么一点呀？
No, you can forget your next month's pay
连下个月的都扣光了
This $2 is for your Mark Six
这是给你买奖券用的
You can do what you want
等你中了奖
if you win
想要砸什么东西就砸什么东西
First call for 50m frog stroke finalist
五十公尺蛙式比赛，第一次集合
May, it's your turn!
简静美，又该你了哎！
Try your best
一定要尽全力
I'll back you up!
老师在精神上支持你们
Save your breath, look!
别白费力气了，你看！
Looks like the opposition is weak
看来今年又没有对手了
We lost it every year, it has become a habit!
我们年年都输给山东队，习惯了啦！
Final call for frog stroke finalist
五十公尺蛙式比赛，最后集合
Can we make it this time?
阿贵，有没有把握？
| hope so!
大概有吧！
On your mark!
各就各位！
Set!
预备！
Hurry...!
加油…！
Damn!
果然糗了呀！
Better luck next year!
不要灰心，明年再来！
It's just the beginning!
比赛还刚开始呐！
Next year, may be you'll have a chance
明年吧，明年或许还有机会
Final call for 400m relay finalists
四百公尺混合接力决赛，最后集合
You must go for it, for our school
你们要尽力，替学校争口气
Lose it!
我看这次又输定了
Shut your mouth!
闭上你的乌鸦嘴！
Set!
预备！
Yiu King, hurry up!
加油呀，姚琼，加油呀！
Hurry...!
加油…！
You're winning, why the sigh
你们赢了，还唉声叹气
Win!
又赢了！
The loneliest man is the invincible
自古英雄多寂寞
Hurry up... May...!
加油…简静美…快一点…！
Don't panic, I'll wait for you!
不要急，我等你！
May, hurry up!
简静美，你一定要快哪！
| could have let you win
放水都还赢，没办法
Get out!
死啦！
My super power is too terrifying
原来我的超能力那么厉害
Let's leave or you'll have a heart attack
我们走吧，再看下去，你会脑充血的
Hurry up!
快点哪，快点！
Hurry up...!
好啊…快点去给她们加油，快点！
What're you doing?
大山婆，你搞什么鬼呀？
Hurry it up!
戴卓怡，加油！
Hurry...!
加油…！
We've made it!
我赢了！
How's our performance?
老师，我们表现不错吧？
Brilliant!
精彩，厉害！
Didn't think I had it in me!
看不出我还真有潜力哎！
It's brilliant!
果然厉害！
It's better if you can win the rest of the match
不过赢到下一场比赛，就更好了
What if we can?
赢了又怎么样？
I'll invite you all to a tour!
带你们去郊游，烤肉！
Dynamic, this time we'll make it
努力努力，达到目的，争取第一
Lucky they missed!
还好没进！
Keep it up, keep it up!
狠一点，打狠一点！
What's wrong?
你怎么啦？
It hurts!
好痛啊！
Good!
好啊！
We've done it again!
我们又赢了！
Time's almost up
时间快到了
I'll show you what I've got
好，你出狠招，我出怪招
What's up?
怎么回事啊？
I kill!
我杀！
This is the final match: High dive
现在举行高板跳水决赛
Piece of cake, we'll win this one
我们赢定了，等着看好戏！
Alright?
是吗？
I'm afraid of heights!
我有惧高症啊！
Thanks!
谢谢捧场！
Bravo!
好棒啊！
Stop pulling my leg!
你们老是整我！
| can't swim!
糟了，我不会游泳，救命呀！
Help...!
救命呀…！
Don't you want to buy him breakfast?
想不想让老师请吃早餐呀？
We do!
想啊！
Here comes the teacher
老师来了！
I'll help you, sir!
老师，我帮你拿！
Do you think you know
老师，你的见闻学识
just about everything?
是不是比我们丰富呀？
Theoretically, yes
理论上应该是的
Alright, now do you want a bet?
那么我跟你打赌
If you don't know it, you lose $500,
如果你答不出，你输五百
otherwise I'll lost $250
我答不出我输两百五
- Fair? - Okay, give me the problem!
怎么样？ 好，你出题！
What's the name of the animal
听清楚了，世界上哪种动物
has 6 heads, 5 horns, 3 hands and 8 mouths?
有六个头，五只角，八张嘴，三只手
Is there such a thing?
有吗？我猜不到
| give up, here's the $500!
我输五百！
What is it?
到底是什么？
| don't know, so I lose $250!
我也不知道，所以我输你两百五
Okay, breakfast is on the house
好，老师请客吃早餐
- How are you? - Morning!
你…你好！ 早晨！
| was terrible last time!
上一次我把她整得好惨
| think I should apologise to her
我应该向她道歉才对
Don't do it!
不要啦！
Shut up!
别怕啦！
Let me wipe your sweat
老师，你脸上好多汗，我帮你擦一擦
Sir!
康老师！
You look so good now!
你看，这样不是好看多了！
We're going over there!
走，我们去听音乐吧！
Let's go, bye!
走了…拜拜！
Morning, Miss Lo!
老老师，你好！
| sincerely apologise for what I did last time
我为上次的事情向你道歉
She's smiling?
她笑？
What does it mean?
笑代表什么意思？
I'll smile too!
我也笑！
There's a stain on your face!
擦掉你的口红印吧！
It must be those naughty girls
对不起，又是那些小捣蛋整我
"It's sunny, the sea is calm"
（天气完全晴朗平静大海）
"The sky is blue"
（天际蔚蓝一片美）
"And our love is sweet and innocent"
（掀起温馨天真的爱情）
"We dance together"
（携着你手一起齐来共舞）
"Like the flying birds in sky"
（似天空小鸟在飞）
"Naughty boys and girls are madly in love"
（偷看顽皮男女狂热地恋）
"They become pairs”
（相爱变成一对对）
"Sharing the innocent love"
（痴痴分享天真的爱情）
"Love is fascinating"
（甜蜜美境 驱使人陶醉）
"And we are fascinated in love"
（醉于此美境里）
"Innocent love is so weak"
（纯真的这份爱 如此脆弱）
"It's like a flying kite"
（天真的爱似风筝）
"Suddenly breaks apart and drifts in air"
（时刻都会断线飘于风里）
"Going away with dream"
（一切美梦亦同誓去）
"Now everyone is fascinated"
（此际人人陶醉如在梦境）
"How can one resist love?"
（春意醉人怎抗拒）
"So cherish the innocent love today"
（珍惜今天天真的爱情）
"If love is gone one day,"
（如欲爱恋他朝完全誓去）
"and you can remember it someday"
（追忆于记忆里）
Let me help you with your bags
老师，我们帮你拿行李
Did you buy salt fish!
你去买咸鱼啊！
Why?
为什么要买咸鱼呀？
Not for us, for Miss Lo
不是我们要的，是老老师要买的
Why doesn't she buy it herself?
她自己为什么不去买？
She asked you to buy it for her?
她没有带钱，要你先帮她买呀！
She'll pay you back!
回去再还你钱嘛！
Hurry up
快点去呀！
Where's the shop?
哪有土产店呢？
It's over there
前面转角就有一家
Look for it yourself!
自己找吧，走！
Where's Mr Hong?
你们老师呢？
He says he's staying!
他说他不走了！
He'll live in the wilderness
从此隐居深山野林
He may join the monastery
当和尚去了
Wait for me... please wait!
不要开船…等等我！
I've bought the salt fish!
我已经买了咸鱼回来了！
It's the last one
这是最后一班船
What should I do?
开走了，我怎么办？
Wait for me!
等等我！
Good bye!
莎约娜拉！ 再见！
You've screwed things up again
那群丫头整死我了
I'll fix you tomorrow at school
明天到学校要她们好看
Hi!
有礼！
Help...!
救命呀…！
I've already saved your life!
我已经在救你的命啦！
Who're you?
你…你是谁呀？
I'm You!
我就是你呀！
What?
什么？
I'm you and you're me!
我就是你，你就是我！
You! Me! Stop playing games!
一下你，一下我，你耍我呀？
| won't do something like that
我耍猪、耍狗
not even to myself!
也不会耍我自己呀！
In a word, I am your ancestor
总之我是你的前世
and you're my descendant, understand?
你是我的后世，明白吗？
No!
不明白！
| don't understand why you look so terrible?
我不明白为什么上辈子像你这么丑！
Terrible?
我丑吗？
In the Ching Dynasty, I'm a real gentleman
在咸丰年间，人人称赞我温文儒雅
Kind and gentle,
风流倜傥
| wanted to join the government
可惜我无心风月，醉心功名
But I failed and died in grief
结果为功名而含恨
Fortunately, I was a kind man
好在我为人最有爱心
and charitable man
平日善积阴德
That's why you're gifted with super powers
要不今日你怎么会有超能力
So the power was given by you
原来超能力是你带给我的？
Correct!
正是！
You've really set me up!
你把我害得好惨哪！
| was kicked out of school
我从小被人家退学
Kicked out of football matches
打球被人家赶出场
| had to compensate for medical fees in fights
打架要赔医药费
| paid for breakage in my work
做什么打烂什么，赔钱赔到倾家荡产
| was a pervert with girls
追女友被人家骂色情狂
All because of you!
都是你害的！
Don't get too excited!
你不要激动！
Thank you very much for your super powers
你的超能力把我搞得鸡飞狗跳
Please take it back!
我看你还是收回吧！
| want to be normal!
我要做个正常人…！
To be normal...!
我要正常…！
Damn, I am late!
糟了，迟到了！
It was thundering last night
昨晚雷电交加
Too bad Mr Hong had to sleep alone!
老师干柴烈火一个人，准惨啰！
A toast for the grand achievement of the club!
干杯，为卑鄙会又一伟大杰作干杯！
Cheers!
干杯！
Come and have a drink, sir!
老师，你也来一杯吧！
Sit down!
回去坐好！
So you're celebrating your nasty tricks!
耍老师，还开香槟庆祝！
You people are hopeless
你们真是无药可救
You don't really deserve my love to you
枉费我为你们付出这么多爱心
Love to us? You love only Miss Lo!
爱心？老老师你也爱呀，你真博爱哦
You only know how to make a fool of me
你们有什么用
Can't you do anything decent
想办法整人最行，正经事一样都不会
Didn't we win the Aquatic Meet!
怎么会呢？我们游泳比赛赢了呀！
If I didn't apply my super powers
游泳赛要不是我用超能力帮助你们
You'll win nothing
你们会赢？
Super powers? Can you believe that? Can you?
超能力，你们相不相信超能力呀？
| never lie, let me show you
老师从来不说大话，让你们看
Open the door!
开门！
Headmaster!
校长！
| thought you're late!
我还以为你迟到了！
Stop the face!
不准笑！
Superman! I thought you're impudent
超能力，老师你就别再吹牛了
Don't laugh...!
不准笑…！
The fan!
风扇！
Duster!
粉刷！
I'm normal!
我正常了！
I'm normal...!
我正常了…！
I'm so happy, I've become normal!
我好高兴，我正常了…！
Let me buy you all lunch
我请你们到福利社吃东西
Help yourselves!
随便你们吃，算我请客！
I'm normal...!
我正常了…！
Is he actually normal or not
会长，他到底是正常，还是不正常？
He has never been normal!
他从来没有正常过！
It must be us!
一定是我们把他整得太过份了！
He's gone crazy!
脑袋“痴线”了！
Let's eat!
我请大家吃东西，快…！
Where's uncle Tang?
邓伯呢？
The price is too much
太离谱了吧，平常才二十块
Where has Tang gone?
邓伯在哪里？
Bread, soft drinks, lunch box!
面包、汽水、便当，快来买呀！
Lunch box $20, soft drinks!
便当二十块，汽水…！
Sir!
康老师！
What's going on?
邓伯，你怎么会这样？
| was on leave for three days
我请假回乡下才三天
They fired me when I came back
回来就说不准我做了
No wonder prices have gone up so quickly
怪不得马上涨价
They called this Modern Management
他们说要换什么“新式企业”经营
To increase the profit of the school!
增加学校利润！
| must talk to the Headmistress
好，我去问校长
It's no use
没用的
The Headmistress trusted the Deputy
那个校长就是相信那个猪头副校长
He tried to get rid of me for quite some time
那个讨厌鬼想弄走我好久
That is his nephew
里面其中一个是他的侄子来的
Up there, go up
阿叔，在上面呀，上去坐吧
The Deputy knows only money
猪头只知道刮钱，以后我们要赔钱了
You better stay here from now on
邓伯，以后你来卖东西，我们来买
We'll buy 40 cans of drinks!
汽水四十罐，来…大家拿汽水！
Let's finish it!
你也一罐…！
It's against school regulations
学校规定
to buy from hawkers
在校内不准向在街边小贩买零食
You better buy it from the snack shop!
要喝汽水到福利社去买！
It's me who invited them to have a drink
不关她们的事，是我请她们喝的
Help yourselves!
来，拿汽水，大家尽量喝，不要客气
The food is cheaper over there!
这边的价钱比福利社便宜一半呀！
Come on!
快到这边买！
The food is cheaper here!
要吃便宜的过来，那边的好！
Don't go...!
不要走，回来…别走啊！
Free drinks for those who eat here!
谁帮忙邓伯的，我请她喝汽水！
Please don't go!
别走…完了！
We've done something decent today
今天做了一件正义的事
We better do something mean
如果不做一件卑鄙的事
or it'll be against the principle of the club
就有违我们卑鄙会的宗旨
You're right!
没错！
Is the letter ready?
信写好了没有？
OK!
好啦！
Is he alone?
他一个人在里面
Yes!
进去！
It's the school's open day next week
老师，下礼拜学校开放日
We want to invite the boys next door to join us
我们想请隔壁学校男生来参观
It's alright!
应该的！
And their teacher, Miss Lo!
还有他们的老师
Miss Lo!
那个老老师呀！
The invitation cards are ready, please sign it
我们邀请信都写好了，只要你签个名
Sign it here!
签个名！
Here!
这里！
It not convenient for us to go there
老师，我们不方便在和尚学校出入
Would you please give it to Miss Lo!
不如你帮我们送邀请卡给老老师啊！
Okay, I'll give it to her!
好，等一下我送去！
Thank you very much!
好，麻烦你啰！
Miss Lo!
老老师！
What can I do for you?
康老师有什么事吗？
| want to...
我想邀请你参加…
See for yourself!
你自己看好了！
Miss Lo, you're my everything
老老师，你是我的干炒牛河
| can't go on without you
我是你的竿柴烈火
| want to give you a big hug and kiss you
我要咬你、吃你，好过烤鸭三吃
because I am crazy about you
爱得越深，情感越深
| am paralysed by your love
爱情好像打了麻醉针
I'll show the world my love for you
我要将我对你的爱，向大众公开
| heartily invite you to the orgy next week
所以诚心邀请你参加
It's my orgy open day
下星期日由我主办的性开放日
Orgy open day?
性开放日呀？
Oops, it's open day!
是开放日！
You and me are going to have a good time
君子坦荡荡，我要与你一齐去放荡
I'll invite
那天，我还会叫陈龙先生
Lady P
娇凤姑娘一齐来放荡
Crazy about you, Sam Hong
狂恋你的人，康心贵
Don't go, it's obscene!
这么下流的地方，你千万不要去呀！
Obscene?
什么下流？
We've done it every year,
我们开放日，每年举办
a lot of people come too
有好多人参加
You can come if you're interested!
你们也可以一齐来呀！
You can count me out!
我参加鬼才参加呐！ 亏你还是个老师
Mr Hong!
康老师！
Is this invitation letter really written by you?
这就是你的邀请函？
Yes, can't you see my signature?
是呀，你没看到我的签名吗？
Please come!
你来不来啊？
And play with my girls, it's fun
跟我的学生在一起，很好玩的
Play with yourself, you creep!
玩你的头，你这个色情狂！
What can I say, Sam?
你真是下流！
He's a low down creep!
何止下流，简直是不入流
To write something like that
这样的中文都写得出来
He has shamed the school
简直是丢尽学校的脸
This letter...
校长，那封信…
It's not written by you?
不是你写的吗？
Not true!
你还敢说不是！
It's true, it's not written by me...
校长，那封信的确不是我写的，那是
It's the girls who set you up!
那是你的学生想整你啰！
You can do better than that, Sam
人都是想推卸责任
Headmistress
校长
I'm sorry, Sam!
心贵，对不起！
Yes, I understand!
不要讲啦，我明白！
It'll be my last day here!
我教到今天啦！
It's his doomsday...!
老师来了…！
Sit down!
快点坐好！
Good afternoon, Sir!
老师，午安！
Good afternoon, class!
各位同学，午安！
Who wrote this letter?
这封信是那个写的？
In fact I know who wrote it
其实看笔迹，我已经知道是那个写的
But I want her to admit it
我只是希望她能够举手承认
It's not a shame to admit something you've done
既然敢做，就要承认
That is the code of a gentleman
光明磊落，乃是正人君子的行为
Only sneaky people
只有那种偷鸡摸狗的鼠辈小人
would deny their responsibilities
才不敢对自己所做的事情负起责任
But I do believe
但是我相信
nothing of the kind is here
我们班上同学没有一个是这样的人
It's me!
老师，是我！
Good!
好！
Don't you know
简静美，你知不知道你写这封信
you've made a big mistake
犯了好大的错误？
Sir, I...!
老师，我不知道！
Let me tell you
你不知道，我告诉你
It's your grammar
你写白字
"I couldn't go on without you” is wrong
干柴烈火的干，是干湿的“干”
It should be "I can't...
不是竹竿的“竿”
It's not
还有，我们邀请陈龙先生的邀字
"I should invite Mr X_.."
这个字你也写错了
It should be "I shall...”
不要妖怪的怪的“妖”！
But don't do it again
以后不要再犯同样的错误
We're Chinese
我们身为中国人
We must be good at our mother tongue
连中文都学不好，会被人家耻笑的
Maybe it's my fault
或许是我的错
Something is wrong with my teaching method
我的教导方法有错误
| am not doing it right
我没有能力教好你们
In order not to ruin your future
为了不要耽误大家的前途
This is going to be my last day
今天这堂课是我最后一次教大家
| hope the new teacher will be better than me
我希望新来的老师，比我更有办法
To show you the right way!
更有能力，把大家教好！
Let's not waste more time
好了，不要浪费时间了
Please turn to page 20
大家打开第二十页
Sir!
老师！
So you've done
想不到最后一堂课
it again!
还被你们整，我真蠢
Damn, this is the oldest trick
这招邓伯已经告诉我方法
What's wrong with me?
我都知道了，我还会…
Why are you crying?
你们干嘛哭啊？
It's me who got fired
我被人家炒鱿鱼，我都没哭
Stop crying!
不要哭了！
Your eyes will swell, won't be pretty
哭肿了眼睛不漂亮
The boys next door won't like it
隔壁的和尚不要你们啰！
Sorry, sir!
老师，对不起！
"He looks at me, he loves me"
（他的眼神 他的爱心）
"He always pretend angry for me"
（常为我装愤恨）
"He bears the pain and smiles at me"
（转笑颜 开心笑 苦楚尽忍）
"He can sacrifice himself for others"
（舍己爱人 义重情真）
"He makes me feel sorry"
（能令我改错误）
"And guides me back to right way"
（走正途 去复勤 得他道引）
"| owe him a lot but I never pay him back"
（欠下似海深恩 未偿还并抱憾）
"I fool around yesterday”
（发现昨天 胡混）
"And I realize what's wrong today"
（到今天 明白到怎去做人）
"His words are like a light"
（他的训言 似像明灯）
"Always light up my life cast away the darkness"
（长在我心照亮 得永恒 驱黑暗）
"Lead me to the bright"
（光辉路引）
What's wrong?
你们怎么啦？
What've you been doing?
你们在搞什么鬼呀？
You look exhausted
看你们一个个都没精神的样子
What a sunny day,
今天是艳阳天
let's go to the disco!
一齐去跳的士高，疯狂一下
Daisy will pay!
我们王子高请客
No, we don't feel like dancing
不要了，我们不想跳舞
It's not the end of the world?
干什么，难道世界末日到啦？
Our teacher got fired
因为我们老师被人家炒鱿鱼
It must be because of you
一定是被你们气走的
What's so funny?
有什么好笑的！
It's you who suggested the letter
那天都是你，提议写什么情书的
You don't have to yell
你干嘛那么大声？
| like to
我就这么大声
But you wrote the letter
那封信是你写的
You made me do it
是你逼我写的
You made me do the dirty work for you
我做什么卑鄙的事，都是你逼我的
It's your fault!
你是罪魁祸首！
Okay, stop yelling!
好了，你们两个不要吵了嘛！
Sit down...
坐下…！
Miss Lo is out there!
老老师在那边呐！
Miss Lo!
老老师！
Yes!
什么事啊？
Mr Hong did not write the invitation
老老师，那封邀请信不是康老师写的
It's me who did
是我写的
He's not a bad person
康老师他不是个坏人
He's not a pervert
他也不是色情狂
He's man of affection and kind to others
他对我们好有爱心，又乐于助人
He is great!
他简直是伟大啊！
Would you help us make it up
老师，你帮我们补救啦！
He has lost his job
是呀，他现在又失业
and his love
又失意，又失恋
Everybody misunderstood him
还有，全世界的人误会他
but it's nothing compared to
全世界人误会他都没关系
your misunderstanding against him
连你都误会他
We, representative of the Club
康老师，我们代表全班卑鄙会员
Apologise to you sincerely
专诚向你道歉
We are sorry!
我们对不起你！
We are no good!
我们不好！
Please accept our apologies!
请接受我们的道歉！
It's going to be alright!
没事的，老师！
Come in!
进来坐吧！
Why aren't you
今天又不是假日
in school?
你们不需要到学校去呀？
Let me do it!
我帮你插花吧！
Where's the vase?
花瓶在哪里？
We don't like the substitute teacher
我们根本不喜欢那个猪头代课
He only knows how to swear
对呀，他除了罚人之外
and collect money
就只知道催交学费
What did you do to him?
你们一定又出花样整他了！
Nothing!
没有啊！
It's agreed by all members
经过全体会员一致决议
We've disbanded the club
卑鄙会已经彻底解散了
Is that so?
是吗？
But we've got a new club
不过我们又成立了一个新会
Club Unscrupulous?
是“无耻会”？还是“无聊会”呀？
No! No! No!
不！ 不！ 不！
Club Struggle!
是“奋斗会”！
For our future!
要为前途而奋斗！
For ideals!
为理想而奋斗！
But we do need
但是我们需要一个人
a leader
来领导我们去奋斗
So we organised a class signature campaign
所以我们今天发起一个签名运动
It's most successful
而且是空前的成功
To support
我们发动了全班签名
your reinstatement!
支持你回到学校来呀！
Madam has the original!
正本给校长！
This is the copy!
这份是影印！
We don't want you to go!
老师，我们舍不得你走呀！
Especially me!
我更加舍不得呀！
We've no coach,
我们现在练球都没有人教
our team morale is low
士气好低落
We'll lose
明天校际排球赛
tomorrow's match
我们一定会被淘汰的
We lose everything without you!
你不回来，我们做什么都会失败的
Are you still mad at us?
老师，你还生我们的气呀？
No!
没有没有！
I'll come to your match tomorrow
我明天到球场替你们打气
Great!
好棒！
I'm Sorry!
真不好意思
The girls dated you for me!
要学生帮我约你出来喝咖啡！
I'm so ashamed!
不好意思的是我
My complaints have cost your job!
没想到因为我的关系，害你失业
| can find a new one!
没关系，工作可以再找
But I worry about the girls
重要是那几个小妞知道错了
Mr Nosey!
猪八戒！
Piggy!
小猪哥！
Haven't seen him lately?
怎么看不到我们学校的八戒老师啦？
He sticks his nose too deep
猪八戒偷懒，又好色
and got fired!
被炒鱿鱼了！
He doesn't seemed worried,
不过猪八戒色心又起
after the girls again!
到处在找猪小妹啊！
Looks real nice!
这只母长得不错呀！
But she has no taste
母猪漂亮是漂亮，不过没什么眼光
To choose Mr Nosey
怎么挑只瘦巴巴的猪八戒呢？
Any of us can do better!
找我们其中任何一个，都比他强多啦
You're damn right!
来…喝酒…！
What're you doing?
你要干什么？
I'll make them disappear
给我一分钟，我要他们立刻消失
You better go, punk!
你们几个臭小子，马上滚！
Or else...
不滚的话…！
Or else what?
不滚怎么样？
To take that...
就像这个…
Same as this, nothing left
跟它一样，什么事都没有
Please go on and have fun, goodbye!
你们尽管骂我，拜拜！
My tiny waist!
我的小蛮腰呀！
Does it hurt?
还痛不痛？
Yes!
痛啊，好痛呀！
You need a doctor!
擦了药还痛，你需要看医生哎！
I'll be alright!
不需要了，现在好像又不痛了！
You need plenty of rest, Mr Hong!
我看你需要多休息，康老师！
Don't call me Mr Hong!
不要叫我康老师，叫我Darling
Call me Darling!
Darling是我的英文名字
My name is Darling Hong!
我叫Darling Hong！
I've got to go!
我要走了！
Please stay for dinner!
不要走，留下来吃饭！
No, I've a date
不行呀，我朋友会来接我
Boy friend?
男朋友啊？
There he is!
他已经来了！
Darling!
Darling！
| have to go now, bye!
康老师，我要走了，拜拜！
Don't go!
不要走嘛！
No need, bye!
你多休息嘛，拜拜！
She's back!
她回来了！
Miss Lo...!
老老师…老…！
Madam!
学姐！
Please come in!
请进！
The girls want you back!
学校的学生好想你回去教
But I've...
学姐，那以前…
| know, I've misjudged you
以前的误会我全都清楚
Please come back or they'll be disappointed
心贵，只要你回去，学生才会念书
Okay
我回去是可以
But on one condition
但是你可答应我一件事
What is it?
什么事？
Tang gets the canteen again
福利社交还给邓伯
No problem!
没问题！
Business has been real bad,
自从副校长的侄子接手以后
after my deputy took over
福利社的生意一落千丈
I've considered getting Tang back
我打算找邓伯回来
He deserves it
真是老天有眼
By the way, the volleyball match this year
还有啊，本来今年的排球赛
We have a good chance there
我们是有机会拿冠军的
The girls don't feel like it
那儿知道她们根本没有心思去练球
and we've lost in the heats!
结果连输了好几场呐！
Relax
你放心，明天的决赛
They'll win the game tomorrow!
我一定要她们赢！
Calling Sam [!
前辈子！ 前辈子！ 是我呀！
Please come out!
快出来呀！
Sam (!
前辈子！
Sam |I calling Sam |
BB Call前辈子
What can I do for you?
后辈子BB Call前辈子有何赐教？
It's nice to see you
前辈子，见到你真好
Please give me back my power!
快点还我超能力吧！
But you said
后辈子呀后辈子
you didn't want it
上次是你自己说不要的
So you've changed your mind
现在又出乎尔，反乎尔
| don't need it before!
是啊，原则上我是不想要
Because it's troublesome
因为要了它，我好麻烦
But I need it badly now
不过，有时我又想要
Do you want it or not?
到底你是要，还是不要呀，后辈子？
Best if I have it when I need it
最好是我想要的时候就有
and go when I don't!
不想要的时候就没有
You're asking too much
你这样子耍你的前辈子
God damn it!
只怪我前世没有修好啊！
Please!
前辈子！
Alright, just for old time's sake
好吧，谁叫你就是我，我就是你啊！
Let's make up two codes!
这样，我们先约两个暗号
What code?
什么？
When I hear "I Love You”
当我听到“我爱你”
I'll transmit the power to you
我就把超能力给你
If not?
不要呢？
When I hear "Sorry", I'll withdraw!
听到“对不起”就收回了！
| love you!
“我爱你”
Sorry!
“对不起”
Thanks...!
前辈子…
| love you!
我爱你！
Sorry!
对不起！
I'm abnormal again!
我又不正常啦！
He's coming!
老师来了！
Sir...!
老师…！
What took you so long?
老师，你来迟了！
We're in the final!
我们已经进入决赛了哎！
You'll win it if you have confidence
我说过，只要有信心，一定会赢的
We haven't, look!
我们这场稳输的啦，你看！
It takes tactics more than just muscle
打球是讲技术，不是看个子大
Relax, if you really in trouble
你们放心啦，待会你们万一输了
I'll use my power to help
我用超能力帮助你们
The Power?
超能力？
I'll sneak up on them later
等一下我在上边用超能力帮助你们
Go for it, come!
来…去比赛，快！
St Holy is tough
圣高贵好，圣高贵妙
She'll win the cup!
圣高贵圣高贵得第一…！
It's kickout. Great
这球出界了，好嘢
Shandong, Shandong is overwhelming
山东，山东，来势汹汹
Cool...
好嘢…
It doesn't touch net It can be this way
那有触网呀，这也可以
Idiot
痴线
| love you!
“我爱你”！
Is this his "Power"?
难道老师真的有超能力呀？
It must be!
一定是呀！
Hurry...!
加油…！
| love you!
“我爱你”！
What?
你说什么？
Sorry...!
对不起…！
| love you!
“我爱你”！
Me? At my age!
我这么老，你还爱我？
Sorry...!
对不起…！
What're you
小子，勾引我老婆
trying to do?
又勾引我岳母？你想死！
Sorry...!
对不起…！
I'll show you!
我宰了你！
Sorry!
对不起！
Right, Sir...?
对呀，老师呢…？
Is OK...
行了，比心机…
Take easy!
慢慢来呀！
| love you!
“我爱你”！
What did you say?
你说什么？
Sorry, nothing!
没有没有，没说什么…！
| love you!
“我爱你”！
Not in front of the public!
不要在大庭广众说“你爱我”嘛！
Sorry...!
对不起…！
The power is marvellous!
老师的超能力真棒！
We'll win this one
我们这场球赢定啦！
We'll win!
赢定啦…！
Sir, we'll win!
老师，我们稳赢的！
| love you!
“我爱你”！
I'm Sorry!
对不起，康老师！
It's my fault!
以前的事都是我不对
You've taught me a lesson,
校长已经教训过我了
I'm really sorry
我真是对不起你
It's no way to treat a colleague
大家同事一场，我实在不应该陷害你
I'm sorry!
实在对不起！
You can say what you like but not "Sorry"
你说什么都可以，千万不要说对不起
No, the Headmistress
不是，是校长要叫我向你说
told to say it
“对不起”的
My nephew had been rude to you
还有，我的侄子曾经打过你
I'm Sorry!
实在对不起！
The power!
超能力…！
What power?
超能力是什么战术？
How come we don't know?
老师没教哎！
Please forgive me!
康老师，你原谅我啦！
Alright, I'll forgive you, don't come closer
我已经原谅你了，你不要跟过来
| love you!
“我爱你”！
| don't deserve
对不起，我自问
your love
没什么值得你爱的地方
I'm sorry for what I've done
我专门做“对不起”你的事情
God damn it!
我被你气死了！
If I provoke you
那是我气坏你了
I'm sorry!
实在很对不起！
Alright... don't say it
好了…你不要说了
Come and talk to me!
你跟我来，我让你说个够，来…！
Sorry...!
对不起…！
Yes...!
好…！
Thank you, sir!
老师，谢谢你的超能力！
| did not use my power!
我没有用超能力帮你们哪！
You won the game all by yourselves
是你们的实力赢来的
Ourselves?
是我们？
Us?
我们的实力？
Yes!
是啊！
Congratulations!
恭喜你啊！
Uncle Tang, how are you?
邓伯，你好？
Madam!
学姐！
Welcome back!
欢迎你回来！
Sam!
心贵！
Can you see the difference?
你觉得我今天有什么不同吗？
Attention!
起立！
Good morning, sir!
老师好！
Good morning, class!
各位同学好！
Starting next week
由下个礼拜起
There'll be tuition daily after school
我每天放学之后，会跟大家补课
Be prepared for your exam
等你们大考考完
If the result is good
如果成绩优良
I'll take you all to BBQ
放暑假，我会请大家去露营，庆祝
Good...!
好啊…！
Let's go ashore!
康老师回来了！
Sir!
康老师！
Swimming is difficult!
想不到游泳那么难学
Never mind
不难学
We've got you 3 coaches
我们已经安排一个老师来教你了
Look!
你看！
We'll not be in the way, goodbye!
我们不当电灯泡了，拜拜，走了！
Their good result really is a surprise
想不到这些小女生考得这么好
It's to your credit!
那是你教导有方哦！
No, they've tried real hard
那里，是他们自己努力
I'm taking them to BBQ tomorrow
所以我明天带她们去露营
Hope you will join us!
希望你也能赏脸参加
Yes!
好啊！
Look, they've got our table
他们那些人怎么坐了我们的位子呀？
Give me one minute, I'll show them
给我一分钟，我要他们立刻消失
Remember last time...
不要了，你忘记你上次…
It's different, because of...
这次不同，这次因为…
| love you!
“我爱你”！
You're sitting in my chair, punk!
朋友，你们占了我们的位子了！
So Mr Nosey is here!
就是你害我们失业的
Let's teach him a lesson!
嫌我们上次打得不够重！ 揍他！
How come...?
你…？
I've done my PT lately!
我最近练举重啊！
Please!
请！
"It's summer holidays Let's cheer and applaud"
（开心放暑假欢呼快乐拍掌）
"Let's sing loud"
（共唱歌歌声最响亮）
"Let's get wild"
（情越情尽情共舞 乱唱乱跳莫大紧张）
"I lose my mind I wish I could fly up to sky”™
（此刻满脑是妄想 愿我可一飞到天上）
"Like a free bird"
（似小鸟自由独来独往）
"Everyday is happy"
（天天都开心最乐唱）
"I'll find my sun in mind for my goal”
（今天我为理想 找心中太阳）
"Even I fail, I'll try hard to achieve my goal"
（即使挫败创伤 誓努力要达到理想）
Being an artist, a writer or a musician is not dream
最理想唔系做画家、作家、音乐家
But being a philanthropist is dream
而系做大慈善家，点解呢？
Because a philanthropist is also a millionaire
因为做大慈善家，个个都系千万富翁
"New stars break out everyday"
（天天有新恋放亮发光）
"They shine upon us"
（让每粒星星也闪亮）
"We leave school but we don't know where to go"
（离校园未明未来路向）
"And we won't stay together anymore"
（怕以后散别各一方）
"We have to make big"
（听朝要进入社会 大众应争取向上）
"Let's go together"
（齐步前路齐共同迈进）
"To find out our way"
（应清楚找到我路向）
"I'll find my sun in mind for my goal”
（今天我为理想 找心中太阳）
"Even I fail, I'll try hard to achieve my goal"
（即使挫败创伤 誓努力要达到理想）
It's ideal to be a doctor
做医生最理想了
Why?
为什么？
There're customers complaint in every profession
因为做什么生意都有顾客来投诉
But when a doctor kills his patient
但是医生医死了病人
Nobody comes back for compensation
他们绝不能回来投诉的
Let's give him a big hand!
你们赶快给我拍手啊！
Why don't you dance?
老师，怎么不跳舞啊？
Invite Miss Lo to the floor!
对啦，去请老老师跳舞啦！
Look!
你们看！
We've got company!
那个大个真不要脸，不请自来！
Neglect him!
就当他没来！
Come on, ask Miss Lo to dance!
快去请老老师跳舞啊！
No, she has a boyfriend!
不要了，人家有男朋友了！
Never mind, it's a fair fight!
怕什么，公平竞争的嘛！
Remember the club declaration
你要学我们奋斗会的宗旨
Struggle for your ideal!
为理想而奋斗！
For your future!
为前途而奋斗！
And, for your marriage!
为…为你的终身大事而奋斗！
Yeah, we'll back you up!
是啊，老师，我们都支持你呀！
Go...!
去啦，去请她啦，去…！
We're dance!
我们跳舞去！
"In a crowded beach,"
（挤迫的沙滩里金啡色的肌肤里）
"tan skin is shining with sweat"
（闪烁暑天的汗水）
"But I feel cold I shiver with a dry smile"
（我却觉冷又寒缩起双肩苦笑着）
"Like cold wind is blowing everywhere"
（北风彷佛身边四吹）
Sir, go!
老师，上！
"Where is she now?"
（说爱我百万年的她今爱着谁）
"I won't blame her for taking away the sun"
（我虽不怪她带走旭日）
"But I will blame her"
（却一生怪她）
"For taking my heart away"
（只带走痴痴的心剩低眼泪）
"I cry out loud and loud”
（狂呼 我空虚 空虚）
"I hate myself for being heartbreaking"
（恨极为她心碎）
"If I know the truth,”
（明知结局）
"I won't be a fool”
（何必去做 玩耍器具）
Yeah!
好！
"I cry out loud and loud”
（狂呼 我空虚 空虚）
"It's all her fault"
（怒骂是她不对）
"I choke back my tears"
（强忍眼泪 从此我愿）
"And I wish I could live in pain forever"
（独在痛苦中活下去）
"In a crowded beach,"
（挤迫的沙滩里金啡色的肌肤里）
"tan skin is shining with sweat"
（闪烁暑天的汗水）
"But I feel cold I shiver with a dry smile"
（我却觉冷又寒缩起双肩苦笑着）
"Like cold wind is blowing everywhere"
（北风彷佛身边四吹）
You're on your own
老师，现在要靠你自己了
But we'll support you
我们精神上支持你
Sit down!
坐下！ 坐下！
"Where is she now?"
（说爱我百万年的她今爱着谁）
"I won't blame her for taking away the sun"
（我虽不怪她带走旭日）
"But I will blame her"
（却一生怪她）
Miss Lo...!
老老师…！
"I cry out loud and loud”
（狂呼 我空虚 空虚）
"I hate myself for being heartbreaking"
（恨极为她心碎）
"If I know the truth,”
（明知结局 何必去做）
| love you!
“我爱你”！
Please don't say it in front of the public!
叫你不要在大庭广众说嘛！
I'm blushing!
真糗呀！
Sorry!
对不起！
"I choke back my tears"
（强忍眼泪 从此我愿）
"And I wish I could live in pain forever"
（独在痛苦中活下去）
...love...
我…我爱…我爱…
I'll wait for you in there!
现在不要说嘛，我在里面等你来哦！
"If I know the truth,” My dear!
死鬼！ （明知结局）
"I won't be a fool”
（何必去做 玩耍器具）
"I cry out loud and loud”
（狂呼 我空虚 空虚）
"It's all her fault"
（怒骂是她不对）
"I choke back my tears"
（强忍眼泪 从此我愿）
"And I wish I could live in pain forever"
（独在痛苦中活下去）
"In a crowded beach,"
（挤迫的沙滩里金啡色的肌肤里）
"tan skin is shining with sweat"
（闪烁暑天的汗水）
Help sir!
快想办法呀！
"But I feel cold I shiver with a dry smile"
（我却觉冷又寒缩起双肩苦笑着）
"Like cold wind is blowing everywhere"
（北风彷佛身边四吹）
"Because she vanishes with my warmth"
（只因心中温暖都跟他消失去）
"And leaves me alone"
（今天只得一串泪水）
"Where is she now?"
（说爱我百万年的她因爱着谁）
I've got something
康老师，有句话我不说出来
| must say
会不舒服的
Maybe you won't like it, it's...
虽然我知道你不会喜欢我，但是…
| love you!
“我爱你”！
Please win this one for me!
为了我，你要努力呀！
"But I will blame her"
（却一生怪她）
"for taking my heart away"
（只带走痴痴的心剩低眼泪）
"I cry out loud and loud”
（狂呼 我空虚 空虚）
"I hate myself for being heartbreaking"
（恨极为她心碎）
"If I know the truth,”
（明知结局）
"I won't be a fool”
（何必去做 玩耍器具）
"I cried out loud and loud”
（狂呼 我空虚 空虚）
"It's all her fault"
（怒骂是她不对）
"I choke back my tears"
（强忍眼泪 从此我愿）
Are you alright?
你没事吧？
Let's go, what's wrong!
你看什么，走了啦！ 走呀！
Damn, I've forgotten my camera!
糟了，我忘记拿相机了啊！
You run faster, Mr Hong!
老师，你腿长，你帮我们拿一下嘛！
OK...!
好…！
Damn, they've done it again!
糟了，又被耍了！
Wait for me...!
等等我呀…！
Goodbye sir!
老师，再见！
Give me a break, will you?
你们这些小鬼，到结束还整老师！
Look behind you!
老师，你看后面呀！
Sir!
康老师！
We love you, sir!
老师，我爱你！
Why you leave me behind?
你怎么不把我留下？
Mr Hong!
康老师！
Miss Lo!
老老师！
You're here at last!
我终有一天等到你！